<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Octopusdeploy on Get Amongst It!</title>
    <link>http://www.example.com/tags/octopusdeploy/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Octopusdeploy on Get Amongst It!</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 18 Apr 2017 06:19:52 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://www.example.com/tags/octopusdeploy/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Setting up Octopus Deploy with a Service Principal - Azure CLI</title>
      <link>http://www.example.com/2017/04/18/setting-up-octopus-deploy-with-a-service-principal/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Apr 2017 06:19:52 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.example.com/2017/04/18/setting-up-octopus-deploy-with-a-service-principal/</guid>
      <description>I just was chatting to my mate Rob Pearson who was giving me some tips on setting up Azure with Octopus Deploy. In my case I was trying to set up a service account to do some deployments. I had already created a service account within my Active Directory with the relevant permissions. Rob pointed me to the Octopus Deploy docoumentation but I was struggling with the Azure Portal.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Creating an OSS Splunk App Part 1: Setting up</title>
      <link>http://www.example.com/2016/11/24/creating-an-oss-splunk-app-part-1-setup/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Nov 2016 21:33:45 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.example.com/2016/11/24/creating-an-oss-splunk-app-part-1-setup/</guid>
      <description>Octocat by jglovier &amp;amp; JohnCreek
This is the next instalment of series of posts related to building your our Open Source app for [Splunk](). My initial thoughts are over here, and I hope to structure the series as follows:
 [Part 1 - Setting up a repository and build on Github for a Splunk app](). Part 2 - Getting data into Splunk via an AddOn/Modular Input Part 3 - Securing credentials for an AddOn/Modular Input Part 4 - Dashboards Redux Part 5 - Deployment Considerations Part 6 - Splunk App Certification  Getting Started Many people would probably start hacking away at this point, however I thought I would take a step back and tackle this from a quality point of view.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Redux - Octopus Deploy Splunk App</title>
      <link>http://www.example.com/2016/11/07/redux-octopus-deploy-splunk-app/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 07 Nov 2016 09:53:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.example.com/2016/11/07/redux-octopus-deploy-splunk-app/</guid>
      <description>Over 12 months ago, I released a cutdown version of a Splunk App that targeted Octopus Deploy. I was stoked when I won an award at .conf 2015.
Since then I have been able to work with a great crew such as Grigori Melnik, Andy Nortrup, Logan, David P. plus many more to release Splunk AppInspect.
Also, I have had more and more questions and queries about running the Octopus Deploy app in a distributed Splunk environment.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Octopus Deploy Template for Splunk Event Collector</title>
      <link>http://www.example.com/2016/05/17/octopus-deploy-step-template-for-event-collector/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 May 2016 06:49:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.example.com/2016/05/17/octopus-deploy-step-template-for-event-collector/</guid>
      <description> Recently I had to revisit an old deployment with Octopus Deploy, and it had been a while&amp;hellip;. I had a requirement to log what was going on to a Splunk instance. Realising I had not shared some previous code, I threw together an Octopus Deploy Step Template for the Splunk Event Collector.
It is easy to setup&amp;hellip;
And easy to query in Splunk&amp;hellip; Get Amongst It!! </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Introducing the Splunk Add-On for Octopus Deploy</title>
      <link>http://www.example.com/2015/06/25/introducing-the-splunk-add-on-for-octopus-deploy/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 Jun 2015 10:19:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.example.com/2015/06/25/introducing-the-splunk-add-on-for-octopus-deploy/</guid>
      <description>It&amp;rsquo;s no secret to those who know me well, I enjoy the delight of a seamless deployment. The team over at Octopus Deploy have toiled for a number of years developing a tool and educating the wider .Net community about the benefits of a repeatable deployment.
Another aspect of tech I love, is structured logging. In particular the detailed visibility it provides into our solutions and what they are really up to.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>