<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Octopusdeploy on Get Amongst It!!</title>
    <link>https://blog.merbla.com/categories/octopusdeploy/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Octopusdeploy on Get Amongst It!!</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 18 Apr 2017 06:19:52 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://blog.merbla.com/categories/octopusdeploy/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Setting up Octopus Deploy with a Service Principal - Azure CLI</title>
      <link>https://blog.merbla.com/2017/04/18/setting-up-octopus-deploy-with-a-service-principal/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Apr 2017 06:19:52 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.merbla.com/2017/04/18/setting-up-octopus-deploy-with-a-service-principal/</guid>
      <description>I just was chatting to my mate Rob Pearson who was giving me some tips on setting up Azure with Octopus Deploy. In my case I was trying to set up a service account to do some deployments. I had already created a service account within my Active Directory with the relevant permissions. Rob pointed me to the Octopus Deploy docoumentation but I was struggling with the Azure Portal.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Redux - Octopus Deploy Splunk App</title>
      <link>https://blog.merbla.com/2016/11/07/redux-octopus-deploy-splunk-app/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 07 Nov 2016 09:53:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.merbla.com/2016/11/07/redux-octopus-deploy-splunk-app/</guid>
      <description>Over 12 months ago, I released a cutdown version of a Splunk App that targeted Octopus Deploy. I was stoked when I won an award at .conf 2015.
Since then I have been able to work with a great crew such as Grigori Melnik, Andy Nortrup, Logan, David P. plus many more to release Splunk AppInspect.
Also, I have had more and more questions and queries about running the Octopus Deploy app in a distributed Splunk environment.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Introducing the Splunk Add-On for Octopus Deploy</title>
      <link>https://blog.merbla.com/2015/06/25/introducing-the-splunk-add-on-for-octopus-deploy/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 Jun 2015 10:19:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.merbla.com/2015/06/25/introducing-the-splunk-add-on-for-octopus-deploy/</guid>
      <description>It&amp;rsquo;s no secret to those who know me well, I enjoy the delight of a seamless deployment. The team over at Octopus Deploy have toiled for a number of years developing a tool and educating the wider .Net community about the benefits of a repeatable deployment.
Another aspect of tech I love, is structured logging. In particular the detailed visibility it provides into our solutions and what they are really up to.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>